trainorders.com 2007-12-13

# About Trainorders.com

**Trainorders.com Inc. PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Trainorders.com Inc. recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of Trainorders.com. We created the following policy guidelines with a fundamental respect for our users� right to privacy to guide our relationships with our users. 

_Information Collected by Trainorders.com Inc_

Trainorders.com Inc. collects information about users during their registration; their participation in certain activities on our websites, including our discussion forums; and through the use of cookies. Cookies are only used for statistical accounting purposes and no personal data about the user is collected. When users request pages from our server, our Web server automatically collects some information about the users, including their IP addresses. These addresses are used by computers on the network to send the requested pages to users. In order to access certain portions of our websites, users must register and provide certain voluntary information about themselves. 

_Use of Information_

Trainorders.com will not reveal any personal information that users provide to us to any third party without their permission with following exceptions:

* Actions from the determination of the site administrators appear to be in violation of State and Federal Law.

* Court ordered release of information. 

* As otherwise provided by this privacy policy. 

Trainorders.com Inc. uses users' IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. We also use it to gather broad demographic information about our users in general. This information does not contain anything that can identify users personally. We may combine demographic information supplied by a subscriber at registration with site usage data to provide profiles, in aggregate form, about our users and their preferences in the content of the site and advertising. We may share this composite information with our advertisers to help them better understand our services, but Trainorders.com Inc. does not give advertisers information about individual users of Trainorders.com. 

Using e-mail addresses provided at registration or otherwise, Trainorders.com Inc. periodically sends out e-mail newsletters and promotional e-mail to our users about services and products offered by Trainorders.com. 

Although Trainorders.com Inc. does not specifically seek to obtain any information from children, there are certain areas of our websites that children may visit. We urge children only to give us any information after they have discussed it with their parents. 

_General_

Trainorders.com Inc. is not responsible for the content or the privacy polices of websites to which it may provide links. 

Trainorders.com Inc uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure and to disclose such information only to responsible third parties after permission from the user. 

Trainorders.com Inc offers a member locator system that provides the member's name, login, city, and state to other visitors of the web site. By default the users login name, city and state will be displayed. Trainorders.com Inc offers an opt out feature in the user control panel. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with Trainorders.com, you can contact: http://www.trainorders.com/about/contact
